{"experimentVersion":"micro_debug","participantID":"t","participantAge":"t","participantGender":1,"confirmationCode":"0670836","participantFeedback":"","totalTrials":14,"dataRecordFrequency":0.03999999910593033,"restbreakDuration":5.0,"getReadyDuration":5.0,"trialList":[0,1,2,3,4,5,6,7,8,9,10,11,12,13],"allTrialData":[{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[0],"mapName":"Persistent","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":1,"trialListIndex":[1],"mapName":"InformationScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":2,"trialListIndex":[2],"mapName":"BeforeStartingScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":3,"trialListIndex":[3],"mapName":"ConsentScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":4,"trialListIndex":[4],"mapName":"StartScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":5,"trialListIndex":[5],"mapName":"InstructionsScreen","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[0.0],"responseChoice":[""],"choiceCorrect":[false],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[false],"FLAG_trialError":[false]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Practice","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"No","trialQuestion":"Is this a bird?","trialStimulus":"cheese","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"GetReady","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"No","trialQuestion":"Is this a bird?","trialStimulus":"cheese","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"No","trialQuestion":"Is this a pineapple?","trialStimulus":"cheese","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"Yes","trialQuestion":"Is this a cheese?","trialStimulus":"cheese","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"No","trialQuestion":"Is this a bird?","trialStimulus":"cheese","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"MainTrial","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"No","trialQuestion":"Is this a bird?","trialStimulus":"cheese","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]},{"trialNumber":0,"trialListIndex":[],"mapName":"Exit","doubleRewardTask":false,"trialAnswer":"","trialQuestion":"","trialStimulus":"","possibleTrialAnswers":[],"preDisplayCueTime":1.5,"displayCueTime":2.0,"goCueDelay":1.5,"minDwellAtReward":0.0,"displayMessageTime":1.5,"errorDwellTime":1.5,"goalHitPauseTime":0.0,"finalGoalHitPauseTime":2.0,"pausePriorFeedbackTime":0.30000001192092898,"feedbackFlashDuration":1.2000000476837159,"trialScore":0.0,"maxResponseTime":10.0,"responseTime":[],"responseChoice":[],"choiceCorrect":[],"FLAG_trialTimeout":[],"FLAG_trialError":[]}]}